<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Gurkha</string>
    <string name="text_accounts">All Accounts</string>
    <string name="hint_name">Full Name</string>
    <string name="hint_email">Email</string>
    <string name="hint_password">Password</string>
    <string name="hint_confirm_password">Confirm Password</string>
    <string name="text_login">Login</string>
    <string name="text_register">Register</string>
    <string name="error_message_name">Enter Full Name</string>
    <string name="error_message_contact_no">Enter Contact No</string>
    <string name="error_message_district">Enter District</string>
    <string name="error_message_email">Enter Valid Email</string>
    <string name="error_message_age">Enter Age</string>
    <string name="error_message_password">Enter Password</string>
    <string name="success_message">Registration Successful</string>
    <string name="text_not_member">No account yet? Create one</string>
    <string name="text_already_member">Already a member? Login</string>
    <string name="error_email_exists">Email Already Exists</string>
    <string name="error_password_match">Passwords Does Not Match</string>
    <string name="error_valid_email_password">Sorry! You are not authorised to login</string>
    <string name="facebook_login_error">Sorry! User is registered but not authorized</string>
    <string name="select_awc">Please select Area Welfare Center</string>
    <string name="changed">Password changed!</string>
    <string name="not_changed">Incorrect Email Id</string>

    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="drawer_open">Open</string>
    <string name="drawer_close">Close</string>
    <string name="text_hello">Hello,</string>
    <string name="text_title">Android Tutorials Hub</string>
    <string name="title_activity_maps">Map</string>
    <string name="facebook_app_id">166146894190129</string>
    <string name="google_maps_key"> AIzaSyAhLvnVHbSuGsuaAfaki6BGxUFMn3fb7yc </string>
    <string name="title_activity_last_visit">Map</string>
    <string name="title_activity_search_person">Map</string>
    <string name="xAxis">X Axis:</string>
    <string name="yAxis">Y Axis:</string>
    <string name="zAxis">Z Axis:</string>
    <string name="heading">Heading:</string>
    <string name="pitch">Pitch:</string>
    <string name="roll">Roll:</string>

    <string name="camera_error">This device doesn\'t support Camera2 API.</string>
    <string name="empty"></string>
    <string name="take_picture">Take picture</string>
    <string name="request_permission">This sample needs camera permission.</string>

    <string name="error_timeout">Connection Not Found</string>
    <string name="error_auth_failure">Authorization Failure</string>
    <string name="error_server">Unable to connect with the server</string>
    <string name="error_network">Network not found</string>
    <string name="error_parse">Parsing Not Established</string>


    <string name="started">Started:</string>
    <string name="latitude">Latitude:</string>
    <string name="longitude">Longitude:</string>
    <string name="altitude">Altitude:</string>
    <string name="elapsed_time">Elapsed Time:</string>
    <string name="start">Start</string>
    <string name="stop">Stop</string>
    <string name="gps_enabled">GPS Enabled</string>
    <string name="gps_disabled">GPS Disabled</string>
    <string name="new_run">New Run</string>
    <string name="title_activity_run_list">Run List</string>
    <string name="map">Map</string>
    <string name="run_start">Run Start %s</string>
    <string name="run_started_at_format">Run started at %s</string>
    <string name="run_finish">Run Finish %s</string>
    <string name="run_finished_at_format">Finished on: %1$s </string>
    <string name="title_activity_tracking">Map</string>
    <string name="title_activity_current__location">Map</string>
    <string name="title_activity_on_vehicle">Map</string>
    <string name="title_activity_loader">Map</string>

    <string name="barcode_error_format">"Error reading barcode: %1$s"</string>

    <string name="no_data">No information found.</string>


    <string name="message_write_error">Error Writing Message !</string>
    <string name="message_write_success">Successfully written to Tag !</string>
    <string name="message_write_progress">Writing to Tag..</string>
    <string name="message_tag_detected">NFC Tag Detected !</string>
    <string name="message_read_tag">Read from NFC Tag</string>
    <string name="message_write_tag">Write to NFC Tag</string>
    <string name="message_tap_tag">Tap the NFC Tag to your device !</string>
    <string name="hint_message">Message</string>

    <string name="location_q1">The pensioner is living in a location where it is possible for them to walk easily to access public transport - IF YES SCORE 1, IF NO SCORE 0</string>
    <string name="location_q2">Public transport is available all year - IF YES SCORE 1, IF NO SCORE 0</string>
    <string name="location_q3">An ambulance service or transport that can be made available to hire to take the pensioner to hospital is available in the area - IF YES SCORE 1, IF NO SCORE 0</string>
    <string name="location_q4">A shop selling food items required is within easy walking distance for the pensioner - IF YES SCORE 1, IF NO SCORE 0</string>
    <string name="location_q5">A health post is within easy walking distance for the pensioner - IF YES SCORE 1, IF NO SCORE 0</string>

    <string name="house_and_facilities_q1">The pensioner lives in an earthquake resistant house - IF YES SCORE 2, IF NO SCORE 0</string>
    <string name="house_and_facilities_q2">The pensioner lives in a weather proof house with a CGI roof - IF YES SCORE 2, IF NO SCORE 0</string>
    <string name="house_and_facilities_q3">A toilet exists in, or within easy reach of the pensioner - IF YES SCORE 1, IF NO SCORE 0</string>
    <string name="house_and_facilities_q4">A functioning water tap is in, or close to the house - IF YES SCORE 1, IF NO SCORE 0</string>

    <string name="in_the_home_q1">The pensioner has an adequate bed - IF YES SCORE 1, IF NO SCORE 0</string>
    <string name="in_the_home_q2">The pensioner can get from his/her bed to a chair without help - IF YES SCORE 1, IF NO SCORE 0</string>
    <string name="in_the_home_q3">The pensioner can get to the toilet without help - IF YES SCORE 1, IF NO SCORE 0</string>
    <string name="in_the_home_q4">The pensioner can dress themselves - IF YES SCORE 1, IF NO SCORE 0</string>
    <string name="in_the_home_q5">The pensioner can wash and keep themselves clean without help - IF YES SCORE 1, IF NO SCORE 0</string>
    <string name="in_the_home_q6">The pensioner can climb a flight of stairs - IF YES SCORE 1, IF NO SCORE 0</string>
    <string name="in_the_home_q7">The pensioner has, what would appear to be, safe wiring within the home - IF YES SCORE 1, IF NO SCORE 0</string>
    <string name="in_the_home_q8">The pensioner can do moderate work around the home and look after animals - IF YES SCORE 1, IF NO SCORE 0</string>

    <string name="communication_q1">The pensioner has a mobile phone signal at their home - IF YES SCORE 1, IF NO SCORE 0</string>
    <string name="communication_q2">The pensioner has a mobile telephone and or a fixed line - IF YES SCORE 1, IF NO SCORE 0</string>
    <string name="communication_q3">The pensioner has access to a phone in a neighbouring house with someone who is willing to help - IF YES SCORE 1, IF NO SCORE 0</string>
    <string name="communication_q4">The pensioner can look up and dial numbers on the phone without help - IF YES SCORE 2, IF NO SCORE 0</string>
    <string name="communication_q5">The pensioner can answer receive call but not make them - IF YES SCORE 1, IF NO SCORE 0</string>

    <string name="shopping_q1">The pensioner can plan and do shopping on their own- IF YES SCORE 2, IF NO SCORE 0</string>
    <string name="shopping_q2">The pensioner can only shop independently for small items - IF YES SCORE 1, IF NO SCORE 0</string>

    <string name="food_preparation_cooking_q1">The pensioner can plan, prepare and serve adequate meals - IF YES SCORE 1, IF NO SCORE 0</string>
    <string name="food_preparation_cooking_q2">The pensioner can eat without help - IF YES SCORE 1, IF NO SCORE 0</string>
    <string name="food_preparation_cooking_q3">The pensioner has a smokeless stove - IF YES SCORE 1, IF NO SCORE 0</string>
    <string name="food_preparation_cooking_q4">The pensioner has a kerosene or gas stove and can operate it - IF YES SCORE 1, IF NO SCORE 0</string>

    <string name="laundry_clothes_washing_q1">The pensioner can do their own washing/laundry - IF YES SCORE 1, IF NO SCORE 0</string>

    <string name="getting_about_q1">The pensioner can travel independently on public transport - IF YES SCORE 1, IF NO SCORE 0</string>
    <string name="getting_about_q2">The pensioner can get indepedently to the AWC - IF YES SCORE 1, IF NO SCORE 0</string>

    <string name="medicine_q1">The pensioner is able to take their own medication at the correct time and in the right doses - IF YES SCORE 2, IF NO SCORE 0</string>

    <string name="home_support_q1">The pensioner is supported by a GWS/GWT trained family member who is delivering good support - IF YES SCORE 7, IF NO SCORE 0</string>
    <string name="home_support_q2">The pensioner is supported by a trained non family member delivering good support - IF YES SCORE 5, IF NO SCORE 0</string>
    <string name="home_support_q3">The pensioner is supported by a trained individual who is offering only partial support - IF YES SCORE 3, IF NO SCORE 0</string>
    <string name="home_support_q4">The pensioner is only partially supported by an untrained individual - IF YES SCORE 1, IF NO SCORE 0</string>

    <string name="economic_q1">The pensioner has not borrowed money to buy food - IF YES SCORE 1, IF NO SCORE 0</string>
    <string name="economic_q2">The pensioner has a small income generated from renting out a room, a garden of animals in addition to their welfare pension - IF YES SCORE 1, IF NO SCORE 0</string>
    <string name="economic_q3">The pensioner has limited financial support from relatives - IF YES SCORE 1, IF NO SCORE 0</string>

    <string name="safeguarding_q1">The pensioner is safe from exploitation (financial or other) - IF YES SCORE 1, IF NO SCORE 0</string>
    <string name="safeguarding_q2">The pensioner is safe from discrimination (by age, gender or by cast) - IF YES SCORE 1, IF NO SCORE 0</string>
    <string name="safeguarding_q3">The pensioner is safe from abuse (sexual or physical) - IF YES SCORE 1, IF NO SCORE 0</string>
    <string name="safeguarding_q4">The pensioner is safe from neglect (failure to provide food, shelter) - IF YES SCORE 1, IF NO SCORE 0</string>

    <string name="medical_q1">Medical Conditions are - adequately managed - score 5, partially managed - score 3, not managed - score 0</string>
    <string name="medical_q2">The pensioner can see well enough to perform daily tasks - IF YES SCORE 1, IF NO SCORE 0</string>
    <string name="medical_q3">The pensioner can hear well enough to understand conversation - IF YES SCORE 1, IF NO SCORE 0</string>
    <string name="medical_q4">The pensioner does not regularly require specialist medical treatment at a hospital - IF YES SCORE 1, IF NO SCORE 0</string>
    <string name="medical_q5">The pensioner has been provided with any waking aid or home support devices that have been recommended - IF YES SCORE 1, IF NO SCORE 0</string>
    <string name="medical_q6">The pensioner has no outstanding prescribed medical treatment - IF YES SCORE 3, IF NO SCORE 0</string>
    <string name="all_routes">All routes</string>
    <string name="edit">Edit</string>
    <string name="my_routes">My routes</string>
    <string name="emptyEdittext">This field is required</string>
    <string name="exceeded_storage">Storage space exceeded</string>
    <string name="fab_close">close</string>
    <string name="add_passport_image">Add passport image</string>
    <string name="add_story_image">Add story image</string>
    <string name="your_passport_photo">Your Passport Photo</string>
    <string name="story_images">Your Story Images</string>
    <string name="write_something_about_this_picture">write something about picture</string>
    <string name="done">Done</string>


</resources>